# — SYEFIRA SHOFA ←

MARKETING ANALYST

### **CONTACT**

(818) 736-1863

sshofa@sandiego.edu

https://www.linkedin.com/in/syefira-shofa/

https://sshofa.github.io

### **PROFILE**

Technical Marketing Analyst with a Mathematics background experienced in the video game, consumer electronics and genealogy industries. Familiar with various marketing channels spanning throughout all parts of the marketing funnel. Adept at developing ETL's, mathematical and statistical modeling, and performance reporting.

#### SKILLS

#### Computing

SQL, R, Python

#### **Analytics Tools**

Apache Airflow, GitHub, GitLab, Databricks, AWS Redshift & S3, Tableau, Datorama, Microsoft Power BI

#### **Marketing Channels**

Offline TV, Audio, Display & Video, Programmatic, Social, Search, In-Game Communication, Email, Push, SMS

# EDUCATION & TRAINING

# Georgia Institute of Technology

Masters of Science, Analytics

Anticipated Completion: May 2024

# Georgia Institute of Technology

MicroMasters, Analytics: Essential Tools & Methods

# University of San Diego

Bachelor of Arts, Mathematics

Minors: International Business & Asian Studies

# **EXPERIENCE**

## Marketing Analyst

Activision, 2020-Present

- Designed A/B test and conducted statistical modeling to investigate marketing impact on company KPI's
- Analyzed performance of marketing efforts and worked cross-functionally with stakeholders to implement optimization recommendations
- Owned automated dashboard ETL and partnered with the data visualization team to visualize the data in a simplified manner that still allows for deeper understanding of campaign performance

# Associate Marketing Science Manager

OMD, 2019-2020

Account: Apple, Ancestry

- Designed, tested, deployed and optimized automated data process with data coming in from multiple data sources across all media channels on a global scale
- Developed match market test statistical methodology to test effectiveness of new marketing tactic, Recursive Partitioning model to identify best audience grouping for benchmarks, RMarkdown reporting templates for automated reporting, flighting strategy to optimize media allocation throughout the new fiscal year

### **Analyst**

MediaCom, 2018-2019

Account: PlayStation

- Rebuilt the database, optimized the data process and improved naming conventions
- Developed and automated business intelligence dashboards for data visualization and insight generation
- Connected excel to SQL database, allowing internal teams to obtain data in real time and analyze with customized data for reporting